finnishbabybox.com 2016-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Finnish Baby Box

**Last Update 30.6.2015**

It is important for us to protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains our practices we use to collection, use and disclosure information that we receive when you use our website www.finnishbabybox.co ("Site") and order from us via our Site. In this Privacy Policy we collectively use the term "Services" to refer to our Site and services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites or services, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, all capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

Any information that is collected through our Services is covered by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time that the information is collected. We may change this Privacy Policy. If we make a significant change to this Privacy Policy, we’ll let you know by posting the update on our Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll update the "Last Updated Date" above to indicate when those changes became effective.

**Information Collected or Received from You**

We collect information primarily to make using our services enjoyable and easy, develop the Serivce further, and to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you have an Account).

**Account Information.** When you use our Service or order from us, we’ll collect certain information that can be used to identify you ( "Personally Identifiable Information"). When you engage with our Services, such as, without limitation, registering for e-mail notifications, setting up a shopping cart, or filling out and submitting an online form, you may be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information, such as name, email address, phone number, or home address. Depending on which activity you engage in, the Personally Identifiable Information may be required or optional. We may also collect information that is not considered Personally Identifiable Information because it cannot be used alone to identify you, such as due date or country of residence. If you choose to purchase from us, we also collect certain Personally Identifiable Information, such as credit card number, billing address, shipping address, phone number. If you decide to leave your email with us, we may send you emails regarding our products and services. If you do not want to receive emails, simply unsubscribe from those emails. If you encounter difficulties unsubscribing, please contact us at team@finnishbabybox.co.

**Information Collected Using Cookies and other Web Technologies.** Like many website operators, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies and Web Beacons to collect information. "Cookies" are small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive by a Web server when you access our Services. Those Cookies may include both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that you’ve interacted with our Services. We also use Cookies to observe aggregate use and web traffic on our Services and to adjust and improve our Services. Session Cookies are deleted when you close your browser. Persistent Cookies are saved on your hard drive for fixed period of time. Most browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can change your browser options, so that your browser stops automatically accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept Cookies, you may experience problems accessing certain parts of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we use, may also place their own Cookies on your hard drive. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of Cookies and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties. "Web Beacon" is small graphical element, typically 1 pixel x 1 pixel graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on our Site or in an email. Unlike Cookies, Web Beacons are usually not stored on your hard drive. We use Web Beacon’s to record certain simple actions performed by you, so that we can measure the performance of our Services. A typical use case for Web Beacons is to know whether you opened an email or not, so that we can infer if the email was relevant for you or not.

**Information Related to Use of the Services.** We automatically record certain information about how you use our Services ("Log Data"). Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the web page that you were visiting before accessing our Services, time spent on our pages, the links on our Services that you clicked on and other statistics. We use Log Data to manage our Service and we analyze or engage third parties to analyze Log Data to make our Services better. We may use a person’s IP address to fight inappropriate usage, such as spam or malware. We also use the IP Address to analyze aggregate information on how our Services are used.

**Information Sent by Your Mobile Device.** When you use our Services on a mobile device, your mobile device sends certain information to us, such as device identifier, your settings and operating system. We collect that information as well as information about your use of our Services.

**Location Information.** We collect information about where you are located by, for example, inferring your approximate location from your IP address. We use that information to improve and personalize our Services for you, as well as, assess credit card fraud risks.

**Email communications.** Note that we receive Personally Identifiable Information about you if you send us an email. We do our best to promptly respond to your emails, and when doing so, we’ll use that Personally Identifiable Information to respond to your email.

**Purchase History.** We may also store certain information that you provided in connection with completing your purchase via our Service (e.g., your purchase history, your visits to our Services prior to purchase and certain billing information). We reserve the right to keep such information as long as is appropriate to be compliant with our retention policy or applicable law.

We will not share the Personally Identifiable Information that we collect, except as follows:

**Information Shared with Our Services Providers**. We use third party service providers to manage and provide our Service. These third-parties have access to your Personally Identifiable Information only to perform Services on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose.

**Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions**. Information that we have stored, including your Personally Identifiable Information, is a business asset. Hence, if the ownership of that business asset changes as a result of an merger, acquisition or asset sale, or in the case of discontinuance of business or bankruptcy, your Personally Identifiable Information may be shown or transferred to a third-party, the acquirer of the business asset.

**Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others**. From time to time, we may need to cooperate with governmental officials or private parties to enforce and fulfill the law. We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information about you to governmental officials or private parties as we see necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas); (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the property, rights and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (iii) to stop any activity that we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

You can make choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information and we’ll honor the choices you make. Please note that we cannot provide all Services to you at the best quality, if you decide to not provide us with Personally Identifiable Information that we request.

**Opt-Out.** We may send out e-mails and other communication that promote our Service. You may choose to “opt-out” of receiving those promotional communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication that you receive. There are some communications that you cannot opt out of, since we have to send you that information – e.g. order confirmations, or updates to this Privacy Policy.

**Modifying Your Information.** You can modify or delete your Personally Identifiable Information by sending us an email to team@finnishbabybox.co. We will delete your information as soon as possible, with the exception of some information that may remain archived for our records or as required by law.

We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect the information that we collect from and about you from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When you enter sensitive information on our forms, that data is encrypted using SSL or other technologies. Please note that no method of sending information over the Internet or storing information is fully secure. So, unfortunately, we cannot guarantee a hundred per cent of security.

Our Services link to websites and services of third parties. We’re not responsible for the information that you provide to those third parties. To protect your information you should review the privacy policies of third parties that you access.

Your Personally Identifiable Information may be sent to, and preserved on, servers and computers located outside of jurisdiction, where the privacy laws may not be as protecting as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside of Finland and choose to provide your Personally Identifiable Information to us, we may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to Finland and process it there.

Our Services are not directed to children under 18 and we do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under that age. If we learn that we have collected Personally Identifiable Information of a child under 18, we will delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

Do you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy? If yes, please send us an email at [team@finnishbabybox.co](mailto:team@finnishbabybox.co "team@finnishbabybox.co").

Just enter your email address and we’ll add an extra surprise product to your box if you choose to order. If you're not about to order yet, don't worry - we'll remember your email address for when you do!

**Finnish Baby Box Oy**   
Itälahdenkatu 20 B   
00210 Helsinki   
Finland
